truebluefanclub.com 2014-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Dallas Cowboys

Last Updated: October 21, 2014

NFL Enterprises LLC, the National Football League, the Dallas Cowboys, and the other members of the NFL Family (collectively, “NFL,” “we,” “our,” “us”) respect your privacy and value your trust and confidence.  This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to our websites and online services that link to or post this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Services"), and explains how we collect, use, and disclose information through the Services. By using the Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to NFL properties that do not link to this Privacy Policy (including NFLShop.com and NFLRush.com) or to information collected by the thirty-two individual NFL member clubs (the "Member Clubs").  In some instances, we may direct you to a site that is operated by a third party service provider. Even though the page where you provide information may have the look and feel of the Services, a different privacy policy may govern that information collection by our third party service provider.

NFL Enterprises LLC has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal.  The TRUSTe certification only applies to our sites [www.dallascowboys.com](http://www.dallascowboys.com/), [www.dallascowboysstar.com](http://www.dallascowboysstar.com/), and shop.dallascowboys.com, as well as our Dallas Cowboys Mobile application. If you have questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@dallascowboys.com](mailto:privacy@dallascowboys.com). **  **If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at [**https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request**](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through our websites that link to this privacy policy or mobile applicatons that link to this policy. ur

  1. **Information Collection**
  2. **Use of Information**
  3. **Sharing of Information**
  4. **Tracking Technologies and Cookies**
  5. **Behavioral / Re-targeting**
  6. **Social Networking Services**
  7. **Public Profile**
  8. **Links To Other Websites**
  9. **Security**
  10. **Data Retention**
  11. **Children’s Privacy**
  12. **Communications Preferences and Access**
  13. **Your California Privacy Rights**
  14. **Changes To This Privacy Policy**
  15. **International Users**
  16. **Contact Us**
  17. **Information Collection**

You generally are not required to provide information about yourself when you visit the Services.  However, we may ask you for some or all of the following types of information when you register with our Services, sign up for contests or sweepstakes, participate in surveys, access various content or features, submit comments or content, use a send-to-a-friend feature, or directly contact us with questions or feedback:

  * Contact information, such as name, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone number;
  * Unique identifiers, such as a user name or password;
  * Demographic information, such as gender; device type, operating system version and mobile carrier
  * Financial information, such as credit card or other payment information;
  * Geolocation information;
  * Device Information, such as activity on the device, which applications are running, browsing history, and bookmarks. We also collect device carrier, operating system type and version; This is to help us ensure you have the best browsing experience possible.
  * Communications preferences;
  * Search queries;
  * Comments and other information posted in our interactive online forums;
  * Correspondence and other information that you send to us; and
  * Additional information as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.

We also may collect certain information automatically when you visit the Services, including:

  * Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area;
  * Other unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers;
  * Your browser type and operating system;
  * Sites you visited before and after visiting the Services;
  * Pages you view and links you click on within the Services;
  * Information collected through cookies, web beacons, Local Shared Objects, and other technologies;
  * Information about your interactions with e-mail messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were received, opened, or forwarded; and
  * Standard Server Log Information

  1. **Use of Information**

We may use information that we collect through the Services for a variety of purposes, including to:

  * Provide you with the products, promotions, services, newsletters, and information you request and respond to correspondence that we receive from you;
  * Contact you via email and otherwise about your account, products, services, contests, and events that we think might be of interest to you;
  * Send you promotional material or special offers on our behalf or on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties;
  * Maintain or administer the Services, perform business analyses, or for other internal purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Services, and other products and services we offer;
  * Publish stories, comments, photos, and other information posted in our interactive online features;
  * Process employment applications and inquiries;
  * Customize and personalize your use of the Services; and
  * As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent. 

  1. **Sharing of Information**

We are committed to maintaining your trust, and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share the information we collect.  At times, as described below, we may share your personal information with others for various purposes:

  * **Service Providers:** We may share your information with service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf (such as to host the Services, fulfill orders, provide products and services, manage databases; perform analyses, process credit card payments, provide customer service, or send communications for us). These companies are authorized to use your personal information  _only as necessary to provide  _these services to us.
  * **Subsidiaries and Affiliates:** We may share your information with all members of the NFL Family, including, without limitation, our subsidiaries and affiliates (e.g., NFL Properties LLC, NFL International LLC, NFL Enterprises LLC, NFL Ventures, L.P., and NFL Ventures, Inc.).
  * **Member Clubs:** We may share your information with Member Clubs, each of whom has its own privacy policy, which is available on the Member Club's respective website.
  * **Select Business Partners:**   With your prior permission, we may share your information with select business partners so that they can provide you with special offers, promotional materials, and other materials that may be of interest to you. For example, you may be presented with an opportunity to have certain information shared with our third party business partners when you enter a contest or sweepstakes or elect to receive marketing offers or other information.  If you do not elect to have your information shared, it will not be shared with such third parties.  We take measures to help ensure that our partners protect the confidentiality, integrity, and security of any information we share with them.  However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners, which may use your information for their own purposes. 
  * **Contests and Sweepstakes:**   In some cases, a third party may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Services, and collect your information. In those cases, we urge you to review the third party's privacy policy for that contest or sweepstakes before participating. We take measures to help ensure that our partners protect the confidentiality, integrity, and security of any information we share with them. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners, which may use your information for their own purposes. We recommend you to read their respective privacy policies in advance.
  * **Surveys:** We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site.  If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information [to . . . .]. We use [may use] a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company is [will be] prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.
  * **Third-Party Ad Serving and Audience and Traffic Measurement Services:** We may use third-parties to serve advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users’ online activities over time and across different websites.  To manage your preferences you may opt out here <http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/>.
  * **Business Transfer:** If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, a business reorganization, or similar event, we may transfer your information as part of such transaction.
  * **Administrative or Legal Process:** We may disclose your information to third parties in order to protect the legal rights, safety, and security of the NFL, our corporate affiliates, subsidiaries, business partners, and the users of our Services; enforce our Terms of Use; respond to and resolve claims or complaints; prevent fraud or for risk management purposes; and comply with or respond to law enforcement or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government or other entity, whether or not legally required.
  * **Interactive Features** : We may share information with third parties when you post information to a user profile or a public area of the Services, such as a chat room, forum, blog, or other community tool. If you post to these interactive features, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure that parties who have access to such information will respect your privacy.  Please exercise caution when using these features.
  * **Other Parties With Your Express Consent:** We may share information with third parties when you consent to such sharing.  For example, if you win a contest or sweepstakes, we may ask your permission to publicly post certain information on the Services identifying you as the winner.
  * **Aggregate Information:** We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations.
  * **Geo-Location Data and Services Providers:** We may share your geo-location data with service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf (such as to host the Services, fulfill orders, provide products and services, manage databases; perform analyses, process credit card payments, provide customer service, or send communications for us). These companies are authorized to use your geo-location data  _only as necessary to provide  _these services to us.  If you do not wish to allow us to share your information in this manner please opt-out by contacting us at [[NFLprivacy@nfl.com](mailto:NFLprivacy@nfl.com)
  * **Geo-Location Data and Third Parties:** We may share your geo-location data with third parties for the purpose of them serving you ads for places in your area.  If you do not wish to allow us to share your information in this manner please opt-out by contacting us at [[NFLprivacy@nfl.com](mailto:NFLprivacy@nfl.com)

  1. **Tracking Technologies and Cookies**

  * Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by the NFL and our marketing partners, affiliates, and other service providers such as analytics providers and e-commerce providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We use cookies  for various purposes as described above and in addition to to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference) and for authentication.  Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.
  * As is true of most websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and or clickstream data. [We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. OR We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this [improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.]
  * We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 of Flash to store [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here:<http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>.

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile app.

By using the Services, you consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies.  You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser.  However, if you choose to reject cookies and similar technologies, you may not be able to use certain online products, services or features on the Services. a

  1. **Behavioral / Re-Targeting**

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide youbased upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences.truste.com/) or if located in the European Union click [HERE](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).  Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.

  1. **S** **ocial Networking**

The NFL has worked with certain third-party social media providers to offer you their social networking services through our Services.  For example, you can use third-party social networking services, including but not limited to Facebook, Google+, and others to share information about your experience on our Services with your friends and followers on those social networking services.  These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on our Services.  These third-party social networking services also may notify your friends, both on our Services and on the social networking services themselves, that you are a user of our Services or about your use of our Services, in accordance with applicable law and their own privacy policies.  If you choose to access or make use of third-party social networking services, we may receive information about you that you have made available to those social networking services, including information about your contacts on those social networking services. Your interactions with those social networking services are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

You also may be able to link an account from a social networking service (e.g., Facebook, Google+, Yahoo!) to an account through our Services.  This may allow you to use your credentials from the other site or service to sign in to certain features on our Services.  If you link your account from a third-party site or service, we may collect information from those third-party accounts, and any information that we collect will be governed by this Privacy Policy.

  1. **Public Profile**

The profile you create on our site will be publically accessible unless otherwise indicated.  You may change the privacy settings of your profile through your account portal.

  1. **Links to Other Websites**

The Services may contain links to other websites or online services that are operated and maintained by third parties and that are not under our control of or maintained by us.  Such links do not constitute an endorsement by us of those other websites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to this third-party content.  We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third-party websites or services.

  1. **Security**

We have adopted generally accepted standards to help protect against loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to the information you provide to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) and geo-location.  we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, while we strive to protect your information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to the Services and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your information.

  1. **Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, as needed to provide you the Services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

The NFL’s online properties that are directed to children, such as [NFLRush.com](http://www.nflrush.com/), link to a different privacy policy.

  1. **Communications Preferences and Access**

You may choose to receive promotional emails, newsletters, push notifications, and similar communications from us.  You may opt out of receiving commercial emails from us by clicking on the opt-out or “unsubscribe” link included in the commercial e-mails you receive or by turning of push notifications at the device level.  Please note that opt-out requests may take some time to be effective.  Your opt-out request will not apply to messages that you request or that are not commercial in nature.  For example, we may contact you concerning any purchases you have made with us, even if you opt out of receiving unsolicited commercial email messages.

If your information changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Services, you may request that we update or remove certain information by signing into your account and making the required changes, by emailing our Customer Support at [NFLPrivacy@nfl.com](mailto:NFLPrivacy@nfl.com), or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.  We will respond to your request within 30 days.

You may opt-out of location based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level or by emailing us at [privacy@dallascowboys.net](mailto:privacy@dallascowboys.net)

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

  1. **Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [CAPrivacyRights@nfl.com](mailto:CAPrivacyRights@nfl.com) or write us at CA Privacy Rights, NFL Digital Media Group, 345 Park Avenue, New York, NY 10154.

Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites with which the user communicates.  Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them.  Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, we currently do not take action in response to these signals.  If and when a final standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals. In some cases, third parties may be able to collect information about a user’s online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our Services.

  1. **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Services prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

  1. **International Users**

Please note that the Services are directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States.  While some of these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection as your own, we commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this Policy.

  1. **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of the Services, please contact us by email at [NFLPrivacy@nfl.com](mailto:NFLPrivacy@nfl.com) or:  
NFL Digital Media Group  
345 Park Avenue, 5th Floor  
New York, NY 10154  
Attn: Website Privacy Policy
